Guide to the Elizabeth Gurley Flynn Papers TAM.118
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IX (Addendum): Files Obtained by Rosalyn Baxandall and Helen Camp under the Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), 59256
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 554 - 747 Reel 27, 59361 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 748 - 959 Reel 28, 59360 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 960 - 1118 Reel 28, 59359 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 1119 - 1330 Reel 28, 59358 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 1331 - 1454 Reel 28, 59357 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 1454A - 1612 Reel 28, 59356 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 1613 - 1728 Reel 28, 59355 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 1728A - 1806A Reel 28, 59354 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 1807 - 1935 Reel 28, 59353 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 1936 - 2102 Reel 28, 59352 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 2103 - 2240 Reel 28, 59351 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 2241 - 2371 Reel 28, 59350 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 2372 - 2486 Reel 28, 59349 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 2487 - 2496 (part I) Reel 28, 59348 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 2496 (part II) Reel 28, 59347 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 2496 (part III) Reel 28, 59346 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 2497 - 2607 Reel 28, 59345 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 2608 - 2705 Reel 28, 59344 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 2706 - 2785 Reel 28, 59343 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 2786 - 2835 Reel 28, 59342 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 2836 - 2933 Reel 28, 59341 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 2934 - 3026 Reel 28, 59340 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 3027 - 3109 Reel 28, 59339 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 3110 - 3174 Reel 29, 59338 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 3175 - 3282 Reel 29, 59337 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 3283 - 3393 Reel 29, 59336 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 3394 - 3492 Reel 29, 59335 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 3493 - 3560 Reel 29, 59334 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 3561 - 3633 Reel 29, 59333 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 3634 - 3708 Reel 29, 59332 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 3709 - 3791 Reel 29, 59331 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 3791 - 3852 Reel 29, 59330 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 3853 - 3935 Reel 29, 59329 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 3936 - 4035 Reel 29, 59328 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4036 - 4116 Reel 29, 59327 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4117 - 4202 Reel 29, 59326 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4203 - 4299 Reel 29, 59325 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4300 - 4376 Reel 29, 59324 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4377 - 4479 Reel 29, 59323 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4480 - 4570 Reel 29, 59322 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4571 - 4635 Reel 29, 59321 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4636 - 4710 Reel 29, 59320 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4711 - 4792 Reel 29, 59319 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4793 - 4847 Reel 29, 59318 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4848 - 4930 Reel 29, 59317 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 4931 - 5013 Reel 29, 59316 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5014 - 5122 Reel 29, 59315 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5123 - 5216 Reel 29, 59314 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5217 - 5289 Reel 29, 59313 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5290 - 5316 Reel 29, 59312 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5317 - 5373 Reel 29, 59311 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5374 - 5439 Reel 29, 59310 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5440 - 5503 Reel 29, 59309 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5504 - 5593 Reel 29, 59308 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5594 - 5724 Reel 29, 59307 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5725 - 5810 Reel 30, 59306 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5811 - 5889 Reel 30, 59305 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5890 - 5962 Reel 30, 59304 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 5963 - 6073 Reel 30, 59303 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 6074 - 6176A Reel 30, 59302 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 6177 - 6295 Reel 30, 59301 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 6296 - 6410 Reel 30, 59300 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 6411 - 6528 Reel 30, 59299 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 6529 - 6903 Reel 30, 59298 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 6904 - 7010 Reel 30, 59297 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 7011 - 7191 Reel 30, 59296 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 7192 - 7419 Reel 30, 59295 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 7420 - 7674 Reel 30, 59294 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 7675 - 7753 Reel 30, 59293 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 7754 - 7824 Reel 30, 59292 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 7825 - 7970 Reel 30, 59291 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 7971 - 8097 Reel 30, 59290 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8098 - 8223 Reel 30, 59289 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8224 - 8330 Reel 30, 59288 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8331 - 8430 Reel 30, 59287 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8431 - 8614 Reel 30, 59286 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8615 - 8738 Reel 30, 59285 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8739 - 8861 Reel 30, 59284 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8862 - 8955 Reel 30, 59283 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 8956 - 9055 Reel 30, 59282 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 9056 - 9166 Reel 30, 59281 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 9167 - 9258 Reel 30, 59280 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 9259 - 9381 Reel 30, 59279 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 9382 - 9485 Reel 30, 59278 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: 9486 - 9529 Reel 30, 59277 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: Communist Party Briefs Reel 30, 59276 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Flynn: FOIA File No. 100 - 1696: Subs. Reel 30, 59275 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: FBI: Miscellaneous Documents (Camp Request) Reel 30, 59274 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: FBI NY 100 - 1696 (c. 1941 - 1947) Reel 31, 59273 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: FBI NY 100 - 1696 (c. 1947 - 1951) Reel 31, 59272 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: FBI NY 100 - 1696 (c. 1951 - 1959) Reel 32, 59271 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: FBI NY 100 - 1696 (c. 1960 - 1964) Reel 32, 59270 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Bureau of Prisons Reel 32, 59269 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Central Intelligence Agency Reel 32, 59268 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of Justice: No. 146 - 1 - 51 - 349 Reel 32, 59267 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of Justice: No. 146 - 1 - 51 - 3337 Reel 32, 59266 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of Justice: No. 146 - 1 - 51 - 3337 Additional Pages Reel 32, 59265 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of Justice: Miscellaneous Reel 32, 59264 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of State: Miscellaneous Documents Reel 33, 59263 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of the Army: Miscellaneous Documents (Camp Request) Reel 33, 59262 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of the Navy Reel 33, 59261 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Department of the Treasury: U.S. Customs Service Reel 33 Reel 30, 59260 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: U.S. Parole Commission Reel 33, 59259 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: Intercepted Mail Reel 33, 59258 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Flynn: FOIA Files: "Sanitized Documents"; R. Baxandall v. FBI, DOJ, CIA (CA - 82 - 8736) Reel 33, 59257 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Flynn: Research Files: Unprocessed (box 1), 322697 (Box 13, Box 18, Box 19, Box 20)
  - Flynn: Research Files: Unprocessed (box 2), 322698 (Box 14)
- Series X (Addendum 2): Files from the Reference Center for Marxist Studies Library: (Unprocessed; 1 box), 411619
  - Articles, Including Posthumously Published, 1916-1996; 434678 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Articles About Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, 1950s-1980s; 434679 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Autobiographical Sketch, 1946; 434680 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Birthday Cards, Undated; 434681 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Congressional Campaign, People's Rights Party, Bronx 24th Congressional District, Undated; 434684 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Communist Party USA History Commission: Conclusion of Transcript of EGF Interview; Biographical Notes, 1962, Undated; 434687 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: American Institute for Marxist Studes, re Research on Flynn, 1964-1973; 434689 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Dear Sid (1 letter), 1958; 434691 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Includes Notes from Herbert Aptheker and a Letter to Jim West, 1961-1964; 434694 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Letters (2) from Burt Nelson; Lonnie Nelson (Daughter Correspondence), 1961, 1989, Undated; 434698 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Handwritten Newspaper Columns (3): May Day in Detroit; More on Harvard; Poison Pens, Undated; 434701 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Index Cards Listing Some of Flynn's Published Writings, Undated; 434702 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - "Inventory of Material Received" [by CPUSA?] Note: much of this material has been separated, Undated; 434705 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - League for Mutual Aid: Invitation for a Dinner for Flynn, Feb 24th, 1926, 434708 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Memorial Meeting Invitation (Honoring Flynn and Benjamin Davis; Baltimore, MD), Feb 27, 1965, 434711 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Poetry by Flynn: Includes Poshumous Readings and Performances, 1997, Undated; 434714 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Photographs of Flynn (Photocopies), 1913-1960, Undated; 434716 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Talk: Personal Recollections of the Industrial Workers of the World (15 pp., at New York University), Undated; 434721 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Typescripts of Flynn's Columns in The Worker, 1963-1964, Undated; 434724 (Box 15, Folder 19)